Hello and welcome everybody to these
masterclass about YouTube organic personal
brand growth.
In this masterclass, I'll be covering the
main points that you need to succeed in
YouTube in order to actually
monetize your audience.
Because this is not to become an
influencer, it's to become a businessman.
What we do or what I do is that we turn
business people into influencers, not
influencers into business people.
So I'm not going to teach you about
business, or I'm going to teach you is about
YouTube and how to get more traffic.
But in order to do that, I need to set
the base that you're a business person and
you're looking for sales.
Why? Well, very simple and very easy.
I can give you all the knowledge, and I
can give you all the tactics to become an
influencer and a YouTuber, but that
is not going to work as good for you.
Why? Because is not my specialty.
My specialty. And where I focus is on
helping people like you to make way much more
money with YouTube. That way, if you right
now your business, you're making $10,000
or $20,000 per month, you can double that
down very easily to $40,000 per month in
just six months. This is obviously not
guaranteed, but it's highly probable that you
achieve it. If you apply the steps that
I'm going to give you in this masterclass.
Now, before I start, who am I?
Who is this guy that is going to teach
you about YouTube and is going to tell you
what to do and how to
make money on YouTube?
Well, very simple and very easy.
My name is Benji, and for the last four
years I've been focusing on YouTube and
growing personal brands like Ayman Gazi,
Yami, Denzel Sensei, Alex G and Premier
Prince Leonardo and many, many others.
You see the method that I'm applying here?
I try to apply it in every single market.
Why? Because if it doesn't work on other
languages, that means there is not a bullet
proof method. For example, some strategies
only work in the English market,
specifically on the American one, because
people have certain culture and certain
habits that they apply during the day.
Those habits and culture affect the way that
they see marketing, and they buy things
such as, for example, like this
program that you just bought.
So that's why I went ahead and I created
this method where it doesn't matter the
niche, the language that you're in, even if
you're a man or a woman, if you're young
or older, they won't work for you.
Now that you get it, let's start and let's
kick it in now, for the next hour or 45
minutes, more or less.
I'm going to give you the
introduction to all this World.
I need you to stay focused with me.
So close. Any of the Windows 10, your
friends, partners or relatives that you're
going to take a rest of one hour so
you can focus very well on this class.
Well, with that being said,
let's get into the video.
In my program, YouTube alchemy, we teach
how to generate audience from YouTube
organically. And then
turn them into clients.
Why is that so important?
Because you not only want
traffic from YouTube, okay?
And that's why one of the main things
that I'm going to teach you sources of
traffic, audience alchemy, and
then personal brand positioning.
Now for that, I have here my iPad, which
I'm going to use to give you all the
indications. Let's start
with the very first thing.
Sources of traffic, shall we?
All right. So in YouTube we have different
sources of traffic in these sources.
What we have is several audiences
separate from each other.
For example, we have the browser
of future browser future.
What is browser futures.
Well very simple is the
feed such as an Instagram.
You have the feed where you scroll and scroll
and scroll and you see pictures, reels
and others you have in YouTube the browser
future, which is literally the same as
the feed when you go into your computer
and open YouTube and all these videos
appear. That is the browser future.
If you click on that video, the source
there is going to put on the video is going
to be that that view is
coming from browser futures.
Now when you go into your phone and you
go into into the YouTube, it's very, very
similar. You will have this.
And this is just the feed,
which is the same exact thing.
It looks like Instagram.
You can just scroll, scroll, scroll and
then click on a video and reproduce it.
All right. Now other source of
traffic that we have is SEO.
And why is this so so, so important.
Well this one is based on keywords okay.
So the keywords that we are using
is basically what people need.
And how does that work.
Well have you ever went to YouTube and
search something like how to build an egg or
how to fix a door, or how
to drive on manual car?
Well, that is the very, very, very, very
first thing that people do when they join
YouTube. And this is
called YouTube University.
Okay. Why? Because this concept
turned YouTube into a whole
world of teaching people.
When you don't know how to do something,
all you got to do is just go to YouTube and
type how to do this very thing.
Now another source of traffic is
going to be suggested videos.
Okay. And the suggested videos are the
videos that appear next to each other.
For example, you click on a video on YouTube
and what appears on the on the right.
If you're on computer, that's
what we call suggested videos.
Those videos are suggested based on the
video that you're watching, and also based
on the intentions that you
already have in the past videos.
So, for example, if you watch lately a lot,
a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot of how to pet
a dog, well, you're going to get
videos of that same intention.
Even if you click on a video on smart,
you're going to have recommendations on how
to pet a dog. That's why this strategy
is very, very, very, very powerful.
It makes YouTube completely different
from all the platforms because YouTube
actually studies you very, very well and
doesn't base you on just content consuming,
but actually on content intention.
What that means is that YouTube is
analyzing how you want to behave, and it's
presenting the videos that
you might like to you.
Now how this actually this works.
Just as I told you, the videos there
appear, there are similar based on your
intentions. But there's one trick.
There's one little thing the YouTube uses
and hacks completely the platform, and
nothing makes YouTube outstanding
completely from the other social media.
And that is the neuronal network.
That means the YouTube analyzes old
traffic that you see and creates a profile.
Let's say that this is me right?
And I like a lot to watch.
For example, listen to me and I
like to watch, for example, bike
videos. Well, there is one more thing.
The YouTube is going to recommend me that
I've never, ever, ever, ever watch it
before. What YouTube knows is because
creates all the profiles for all the people.
For example, John John watches
also as for me and bikes.
Now if we go to Mike,
apparently he watches also as smart.
But there is another, another guy
which is Peter that watches as well as
some of me and bikes.
Now what happens here exactly
that John watches also,
for example, do camping.
All right. Mike doesn't watch that.
Mike watches videos about meditate.
Okay. How to meditate.
Yes, but Peter thus watch how to do
camping. So based on this
33%, considering that this is
one, two and three,
this is a 0% because it doesn't, you know,
this one is not the same as this one, but
this one is the same as this one.
So this is another 3%.
YouTube has a 66%
probability that you are going to
watch a how to do camping video.
So what happens is that YouTube
recommends you that video.
And that's how the actual neural
network works in YouTube.
YouTube has two things an
algorithm and a neuronal network.
And this is how it works on
Instagram for the country.
We only have the algorithm, and it's only
based on what we like and what we watch.
And YouTube goes further than that.
YouTube tries to understand your persona
and then tries to recommend content based
on all the people's profile that they
liked, similar to yours, and then bring you
that content. Because YouTube thinks
that you might like it as well.
And normally 99% of the time
YouTube is completely right.
So back to what I was saying.
To suggest it is very, very powerful
because it works with this neuronal network.
And then we have browser future
which is algorithm based.
So as you can see here, we can use
three completely different strategies.
And that's why you probably seen people on
YouTube succeeding very very, very well
without using the same techniques
that I use or that other people use.
For example, you can be on the browser
features and use blogging content, or you can
use educational content and be here,
but also you can be on just the keywords
and helping people. How to solve
a problem and be here as well.
We have the how to solving a problem.
And then we have from the other side from
the country the positioning based on just
keywords. For example
interests such as cooking.
If you search for this word,
what's going to happen?
It's maybe not what you're going to learn.
For example,
let's say we search for video.
We search for whatever video that it's
like three surely desserts that everybody
likes. So when you search for that,
you're going to get that video.
That video is not teaching you anything.
It's just showing you the desserts that
you were looking for and based it on a top
three in the world. Maybe you're educating
yourself because it's more information.
It's valuable information for you, but
it's not teaching you how to do it or
anything like that. You just watching for
entertainment or purely on information and
not education, which are completely
different information from education.
Now, what's going to happen here that this
content is going to go strictly to my
browser is going to
start to get recommended.
So YouTube not only understands the problem
that I have and how to solve them, also
understands the needs that I
have and how to satisfy them.
These are two completely different things.
When I have a problem, I need a solution.
But when I have a need,
I need a satisfaction.
A problem can be fixing something,
doing something, or changing something.
But a need could be literally
as simple as I need to rest.
So that's why I need.
So that's why YouTube recommends me.
Every time that I jump on YouTube.
Because I use YouTube for wrestling cat
videos or entertaining videos or blogging
videos. Why? Because I need to rest.
YouTube understands us and recommends me
cat videos because that's the most I watch
on that platform. So that is a
need, but not a actual problem.
So what are we going to do?
We now going to use the need part.
Why YouTubers do that to entertain people
that joining into the platform just for
purely entertainment.
On our case, we're going to use
YouTube for purely educational.
And that gets me to my second point on
this part where we can understand is the
audience that we're looking for,
the audience we're looking for it.
We're going to understand
it on two main topics.
First, the theory what is are
we looking for in YouTube?
And second, our avatar is highly, highly,
highly, highly, highly probable that if
you are looking for an avatar, you can
understand his problems and you can
understand his problems.
You can use the SEO to target that person.
For example, you've probably seen that Adam
has posted videos about how to build an
asthma myself. Don't
lose asthma or generate,
these mean turmoil on set.
Van van Court. I don't know if I have said
it correctly, but that's more or less the
content. So that content is educational.
It is targeting some people.
That people is you. Why?
Because Adam is looking for this audience
that is trying to learn how to make money
online. So he's understanding his avatar
and his solutions very, very, very well.
Now, the first part that you might not
understood is the theory why educational
content works so well.
When we do a masterclass, imagine that
you're doing the video on how to solve a
problem. For example, imagine I'm doing a
video on how to fix my iPad for example,
if it was broken. So this video
teaches me how to fix an iPod, right?
And this video is five minute long.
All right. And then we
have this all the video.
What is the exact same video okay.
Is the exact same as how to fix an iPod.
But this one is actually 25.
This video is five times more
longer than the video before.
Now why is this important?
Well, because both of them solve the
problem and you might think, well, I might
watch the five minute video because
the five minute video is shorter.
That is audience behavior part number one.
That means that people, when they see
that they have a problem, they will most
likely go to see this video
because it saves them.
It saves them more time
than this video, right?
This video helps me to solve
my problem in five minutes.
While this video helps me to
solve my problem in 25 minutes.
Now that's not how it works actually.
How does it work? Well, there is
where the YouTube algorithm kicks in.
The algorithm wants two things.
People click on the
video two main stats CTR
which is clicks and then engagement.
Or in this case average view duration.
Now YouTube does not really
care about this actually.
What does YouTube really,
really, really care about?
Well, there's this important stat that
nobody talks about, which is the watch.
Then think about it. Why do you two want
people to click on their videos and then
watch them? Well, because
that's how they make money.
If people click on more videos and they
watch for longer, they will consume more
ads. If they consume more
ads due to makes more money.
And also the content on YouTube is more
entertaining and they give the value to the
client. Now, if a client spends less time
on YouTube, that's actually punishing.
Why? Because that means the YouTube can
only show him a small amount of ads.
So YouTube is making less money, and also
that people decided to leave YouTube.
That means that they didn't
enjoy the content into watching.
So the time session is lower.
That's not good for you to.
What YouTube wants is more money.
Yes, but also more value.
And the platform YouTube wants you to
watch, more content to enjoy it and make
money, not to make money.
And you enjoy is the other way around.
Okay? Why? Because like that YouTube
can assure that they're making money.
Why? Because the first value is you.
Is your entertainment or your
engagement on the platform.
If you're really engaging the platform and
you consume a lot of content, that means
you're consuming a lot of value.
If you consume a lot of
value, YouTube is happy.
Why? Because they can put
their ads and make money.
Meanwhile, you enjoy a good content.
Okay, Benji, I understand everything that
you said, but I don't get why this is
important. Well, very, very simple.
This is important because if you go to this
video again, right, how to fix an iPod
and then obviously how to fix that.
But we can see that this
video is longer than this one.
Now where would you click.
You think that you click on this one.
But actually you click on this one not
because you click on it, but because YouTube
will recommend this video.
And how does that work?
Very easy. Pure maths.
If I have the video number one, which is
five minutes and I have the video number to
just 25 minutes, we said that this
video is five times longer than this
one right
now. If you want to make a good retention
here and we remember we want watch time,
not engagement. We don't want this, we
want this, we want more watch time.
We want people to watch more content.
Not that the content that they
watch have more retention.
And what is the difference here?
Very simple. I know this is
confusing, but stick with me.
If someone watches out 100% of this
video right on retention, it's a success.
They watch the whole video now what does
actually YouTube see what actually YouTube
sees? If someone watches the second video
and consumes it for 40% of retention, that
means that the video was not so good
and that this video is definitely
overperforming this one right now.
YouTube. It's not what he sees when
YouTube sees that 40% of 25 minutes, it's
actually ten minutes.
So YouTube is thinking,
Wait a second. Someone consumed 40 minutes
of this video and that was ten minutes
for me. And someone consumed
100% of this video.
But that was five minutes.
I'm actually interested
on promoting this one.
Why? Because for the rule that I just
mentioned before, it gives me more minutes,
it gives me more watch them.
So that means that YouTube wants more content
like this one instead of actually this
one. Therefore, the retention rule and what
you've seen out there on YouTube may not
be completely accurate.
Why, for example, needs to
be searched constantly.
You have to have retention on your videos,
but people don't understand it quite
well. They stick to the percentage,
but they don't stick to the watch.
Then if you just make longer videos, you
will have a higher chance of getting more
watch time without having to have a
perfect retention with a perfect error.
Now, this doesn't apply to everybody.
Obviously, YouTubers needs to make
videos of ten minutes because they're
entertaining, and if they make videos of
40 minutes, they will risk that the people
will get bored during the video because
it's so long and would just leave no matter
the editing and no matter the content.
Okay, then I understand.
Then why would people watch
our videos if they are longer?
Very very very simple.
You are not entertaining, you're educating
and that's what you want to become in
this YouTube university.
You don't want to be another entertainer,
but in this crazy thumbnails and teach
people trying to entertain them with those
thumbnails like, don't show up, Jeanette,
do you mean put on some minute?
No, that doesn't work okay
for this actually work?
What actually works is education and
longer videos with all my clients.
As you can see, Magaji, you own me,
Denzel Fox, Alex G, or El Sensei.
I normally tend to have longer videos.
You won't see a video
less than ten minutes.
Why? Because I need the watch time.
Because the watch time feeds my profile
and gets the platform what they want.
So the platform gives me what I want.
Which are views and subscribers.
Okay. And how does this work?
Very simple. You are educated
in the educated niche.
We don't need to entertain people because
we don't need to entertain people.
We don't have to compete and be extremely
powerful and super charismatic to camera
and talk like very, mysterious
way and, build these theories
because you don't have
to be like that, okay?
Why? Because you don't
need to entertain anybody.
Every person there is watching your
videos are not there to entertain.
They're there to educate because
they're there to educate.
You have an intention which here you don't
have an intention because you have an
intention. People will stick to your
videos and watch it till the end.
And even better, they will come back to
the videos and watch it again because they
want to refresh something
that you teach them.
Let me just put an example.
You understand all this.
This video is what I'm
showing how to fix something.
Now notice the camera quality, notice
the noise and the voice quality.
And listen how this person speaks to camera
and not him speaks to camera with no
charisma at all. Do you think
that that's a good video?
Well, for me it seems not very appealing.
Does it look like a good video, for
example, like this one where I'm sit down.
The spot is very nice.
My voice is very clear.
You can understand everything I say and
I'm trying to be entertaining and engaging.
Now, what if I told you that, for example,
my video, this video right here could
get, let's say, 10,000 views or 100,000
views, but that video specifically got
hundreds of thousands of
views or even millions.
Why does that happen?
Well, because of the problem and the urge
to solve that problem is way much bigger
for the artist or for the person
that is watching that video.
Then the actual barrier that they could
face while listening to a bad audio look
into a bad visual, or seeing a low quality
video, even though if the person doesn't
have any charisma, you will listen to it
because you want to fix that problem.
So that rather that problem is boiled in
an egg, that problem is tiny issues, or
that problem is fixed in
something like this man.
Therefore, what better look
the retention look like?
For example, in an entertaining video
the retention bar looks just like this.
You will watch, watch, watch, watch, watch
what you get born from and then you jump.
But you will never come
back to this video.
Why? Because you already seen
the video and you don't.
You didn't think that it
was very, very entertaining.
Maybe
if the video was very entertaining, you
would watch what what what what what to
watch one until more or less the middle.
Or there's a rule, there's like 60% of
content consumed and then you will skip it.
Would you come back to the video?
Probably not. You already watched it.
Okay. So and it's not a TV show.
It's not. It's not like they would be
watching Superman or The Flash or anything
like that. That actually gives you reasons
to come back because it's a season.
No, it's just content.
It's just a YouTube video because
it's just a YouTube video.
It doesn't give you a reason to come back.
Now, if you're watching this video,
this video has a double attention.
People watch, watch, watch, watch, watch.
They don't. They get frustrated.
Maybe they leave, but they
come back to the video.
Meanwhile here they do not
come back to the video, right?
Why they do not come back here
and they do come back here.
Well, because here they just as I said,
watch the video, but here they have a
problem that they need to solve.
And if they didn't solve that problem, they
will come back again and again and again
and again and again until they solve that
problem and that it's not going to look
like this, like another bar.
No. Is the same person
that is coming back.
And what happens is that that same person
comes back and then watches a little bit
more and then leaves and then comes back
and then watches a little bit more and
then leaves and then comes back
and then watches a little bit more
and then leaves and then comes back.
Why? Because they want to rewatch again.
So it's a restart. Is the retention bar.
How does that work? Well, basically a person
would come back again and keep watching
the video starting from
zero or from any point.
That is interesting. Well, that means that
this video right here, let's say both are
ten minutes. Okay, ten
minutes and ten minutes.
Right. This video right here,
people would have watch it 60%.
That is six minutes. Right.
And they will leave and never come back.
But here to watch the video
fully and even to 120%.
Why? Because they will
watch the ten minutes plus.
They come back again and rewatch the video
again because they want to understand
again what the problem
was and how to solve it.
Maybe you solve the problem and then the
problem go back again, and then you watch
that video on hey, let me see
how this man solved that problem.
Because when I use that
video, I solved it.
So let me come back again to that video,
see it refresh my mind, and what are the
steps that I need to do and then solve my
problem, my machine problem, or whatever
problem that I'm trying to fix.
And people watch more and more and more.
So let's say that it's
just two more minutes now.
The conversation and the information
that we give to YouTube is very, very
appealing. Why this video is getting
12 minutes of retention out of
ten minutes, which that means a
120% off retention,
even though this is not
going to show on the YouTube.
But this is how you to
understand that data.
Now, on the other side, what you will see
is that people see six minutes this video,
but the actual video lasts ten
minutes and that is a 60% retention.
Even though this retention is very good
and very high, YouTube is going to tend to
recommend this video more.
That's why if you're educating, if you are
teaching, you don't need to be engaging.
Why? Because people will
consume your content.
People will actually see your
videos because they need to.
Remember when you were studying
in the high school, okay?
And you needed to solve a math problem or
a physics problem, or even just to know
something about history.
Well, you will watch a video on YouTube
on how to solve that problem, and even
though the teacher wasn't very good at it,
you will stay watching that video until
you actually learn how to do that
math problem or that physics problem.
Now on the entertaining part
you are not doing that.
You just join into YouTube while you're
eating and you watch some video, you put it
there, you watch it
till you eat your food.
And then when you finish with your food,
you just cut the video and then leave to do
something else. But you don't stick until
that video finishes because you want to
finish this. Now, an extra here is that
MrBeast and YouTubers like that are very
good at this. They generate this sensation
and this feeling that you need to finish
that video and they entertain you.
Until that video finishes, you might be
done eating, but you move your plate away
and you stick watching that video
because MrBeast is very entertaining.
That's how the entertainment niche lives,
the entertaining niche entertains, and
therefore what they do is that
they're a master of this craft.
They make people come back
to keep entertaining more.
Now for our side, you don't
need to talk like me on camera.
You don't need to be super good,
super engagement, super entertaining.
Why? Because you aren't educating, right?
I feel like I'm repeating myself
constantly here, but I really want you to
understand this part.
Why? Because this is
your unfair advantage.
What are these unfair advantages?
Well, very simple. First, you have
intention from your clients and your
audience. Second, you have
retention from the platform.
So you don't need to do more.
And third, you have a pain.
And that is the strongest point.
Why? Because when you're done with this 40
minute video where you teach how to solve
a problem and it's going to
recommend you to this audience.
Now, this audience is very, very good.
Why? Because in the
description you will have a CTA
call to action to your landing page,
right to your landing page.
When they join your landing page,
they will have a clear need.
And in that clear need, they will be able
to buy a product for example, it needs to
be has to sell chocolate in
order for people to buy it.
Why? Their audience is of this quality?
Because it's a mass market.
The audience is more young because the
younger people are the people that have time
to watch this videos, and they're
interested on the topics that Mr. BS gives.
Now, your audience might be a little bit
more older and more interested on something
different. Your audience may have money,
and your audience have a clear pain that
they're appealing to, a clear pain
that you can call an appeal to them.
Therefore, you have a YouTube.
These unfair advantages.
So all you got to do to
go on YouTube is teach.
Focus on the educational
content, not entertaining.
You shall not entertain people on YouTube
because it doesn't make any sense.
You are a teacher, not an entertainer.
Getting back to what I was saying
before, this is audience alchemy.
This is how we do magic and we turn
YouTube into a money making machine.
Why? With these steps that I just told
you, these points that are very clear now,
here is the theory that
I just talked about.
And you have to analyze your avatar.
Okay. This is how it works.
Now, how can you apply it?
Well, you have to understand your avatar
very well if you're working, for example,
and, coaching this coaching niche, you
might help people how to solve trauma.
So if we go to YouTube
and we search for how to solve trauma,
how to solve
trauma, you might find this videos for
example, this videos has 2000 200,000 views.
This video then we have 277,000
views which are all the same channel.
Now this one for example has from Doctor
Becky Spellman has 16,000 views and this
one has 11,000 views.
If we keep going, this one
for example has 5 million.
This one has 600 K I'm sorry, that is in
Spanish because my tablet is on Spanish.
But yeah you more or less
understand how to search for this.
So for example let's go and let's
dive more in on some examples.
Let's say you are a seduction coach and
then you teach how people can pick up
girls or boys, let's say girls, because in
this case, I'm a man and I'm looking for
girls how to talk to a girl.
Here you can see the titles that people
are using to position in their content and
actually drive views.
Mastering the art of
conversation with a woman.
Now, as you can see, that title is very
opinion and a position as the first.
We might see that, for example, this video
is 11 minutes and the other ones are six
seven. This one, for example, is 11 minutes
and that's the first one and it doesn't.
And it's not the one that has most views.
For example, this one has 546,000.
This one has more views of
the teaching man fashion.
And this one about this
dot has 2.9 million views.
Now probably because of
this one gives more.
What time YouTube recommends is the most.
Now you see how these
techniques apply to reality.
This obviously is not
a guaranteed science.
Why? Because in marketing and in personal
branding in YouTube, which also have the
highest percentage of success, if we make
a longer video, if we titled it right, if
we do the right content, if we show the
right validation during the video, it's
highly probable that you're going to be more
successful then if you don't do all the
points that I just mentioned, all of these
thumbnails that you see right here and
all this points, you might think, wow,
the Benji, which one is the best title?
Which one is the best thumbnail?
Like, I really want to have the best
one so I can beat everyone in my market.
That is where you're wrong.
You don't need the best title and the best
thumbnail to beat everyone in the market.
You need to more accurate
to a personal brand.
What does that mean? That means that for
example, this guy teaching men's fashion,
he put on the thumbnail, you
are ugly and I love you, right?
So that means that the man is telling the
woman that you're ugly and the woman is
the man I love you. Why?
Because that works in a reverse
psychology, blah blah blah blah blah.
If that's how you want to show yourself,
that's what we should be going to.
But let's see this guy, this guy
went with something very different.
This guy didn't actually put an
interaction between two women.
Why? Because it's not his style.
What's his style? Well, to do these
copywriting techniques, for example, the man is
with a very easy thumbnail.
You can see this one.
This one is very designed, is very
colorful, is perfectly shaped and stuff like
that. And this man is literally just him
showing something on them on the camera.
And it has something written.
That thing written calls your attention
and communicates and talks to you
specifically. They will become obsessed
and you want to make those obsessed, right?
I want to make girls obsessed
because of that need that I have.
He just called my need.
So that's another way of
calling my attention every way.
It's right. In every way it's perfect.
You just have to find the
best that works for you.
So that's why I don't like to copy thumbnails
around there, even if for my clients.
I do that and I mimic formats.
The main idea of the title and
the thumbnail are not copied.
They're based on what my audience
wants and how should I talk to them.
Let's keep searching.
For example, this guy is showing me how
he's on the streets talking to a girl and
says how to approach any girl in public
without being creepy and it says works every
time. Wow. That's why I need
I don't need this videos.
I need to talk to girls.
Why? Because in my title here I thought
how to talk to girls and he just literally
put how to approach any girl.
So for example, if I am a seduction coach
and I want to do a video on how to talk to
girls, I'm not going to name
my video How to Talk to girls.
I'm going to name my video how to approach
girls in public, or how to approach any
girls in public, or the best way
to approach to girls in public.
And I will show an interaction
of me talking to another girl.
Why? Well, because you might think, oh no,
I'm trying to learn how to talk to girls.
Okay, let me dive in that more.
Let me go more in-depth with that.
Why do I want to know
how to talk to girls?
Why do I want to know this?
Because I am feared of talking to a girl.
I am afraid to approach a girl.
So that's where the first keyword appears.
Approach a girl right now.
Why am I afraid to approach a girl?
Because I don't want to.
I'm shy and I don't want to be
creepy nerdy stuff like that.
Second word creepy. Now, if we analyze
this title, this man is attacking more.
My need that I am doing
with how to talk a girl.
I am me as a client, as an audience.
I am looking on how to talk to a girl, but
in my mind, what I actually want is how
to approach a girl. That's why when I type
in how to talk ago, I'll probably scroll,
scroll, scroll and go to this video and
be like, oh, how to approach you go, yes,
that's the video I want
and I'll click on it.
And that is how you differentiate
yourself from the rest.
For example, as you can see here, this
guy is not positioned but has 1.5 million
views now. Why? Because
he has his own style.
If you go on his channel, you can see
that the thumbnails are all the same.
He just creates interaction thumbnails.
That's his style and that's
his way of going with things.
Now he just made me give
back to talk to girls.
Now I'm going to subscribe now.
But back to what I was saying.
If we go to, for example, teachings about
fashion, we can see that this man is doing
more sit down videos and what is not doing
approach is doing these fancy thumbnails
kind of like a magazine style, right?
And join me down. So so for example, all
this stuff I know that I watch here, I can
see that they have a same pattern,
for example, this thumbnail right here
and this icon right here.
Right.
Those thumbnails are very similar.
For example this one too.
So the thumbnails are have a very
similar style, even if you don't see it.
And this is how this man goes with things.
That's his style. Now you
just have to find yours.
And I'll be teaching that more
now here in this training program.
This is how you position to brand.
You have to analyze who your audience is.
You have to understand this, how you position
yourself again, first of all will be
understood here is the main, the main
point which is understanding YouTube, then
understanding, then comprehending with
audience alchemy and then finally
know yourself. I hope that I've
been very clear with this.
Three points. First of all, you
need to understand the platform.
If you don't understand the platform that
you're in, for example, in this case
YouTube, you won't be able to apply
techniques to actually promote your content.
And this applies to every single platform.
Even if you're in Tik Tok on Instagram
or Snapchat, you want to understand the
platform. You want to understand what
does the platform want and how does the
platform promote my content?
Once you understand the platform, you're
going to understand the audience that lives
in that platform. People don't behave the
same on Instagram that they do on YouTube
or for example, Twitter.
Why? It's a different type of
content consuming people on Twitter.
Scroll and read people on Instagram.
Scroll and entertain.
Double tap and keep scrolling.
People on TikTok do the same
thing, but way more faster.
And people on YouTube the different.
They just look for something more than
they can recommend this something.
They click on the video and they
stay watching for a longer period.
That is your audience, and you want to
understand how your audience behave on your
platform and what they're looking for on
that platform, in this case, is YouTube.
So we want to educate.
Why? Because that's what
people are looking for.
Mainly your clients, the ones that
are going to pay you good money.
Now on the third point, for
example, you get to know yourself.
You get to know your
spot, your personal brand.
For example, if I teach here to 4 or 5
seduction coaches, I will have to shift the
content differently from each one.
Each one has his own personality.
Each one has his own style to satisfy a
different niche coming from another angle,
solving the exact same problem.
Now, you might teach me how to get girls
using Tinder or Bumble, or now you might
teach me how to get girls go in
the streets and approaching them.
Those two things solves my problem.
But there are different solutions
to the exact same problem.
That's why the style and the personality,
which means the personal brand is very
important. You got to know yourself.
You can understand where are you
coming from and what you want to do.
The main part for me on YouTube is that
you enjoy creating content as much as I'm
doing right now, given this masterclass,
so you can actually say doing it in a
sustainable way, because
consistency is 50% of the journey.
And that is my last point.
To introduce this point,
let me put an example.
Imagine you want to go to the gym because
you want to get stronger and shape.
Now there's two ways
you're going to do this.
First way is if you go
four times a week, okay,
four times a week, and you also
eat well every day, you are most
likely going to achieve those results.
Why? Because you're applying it.
You're doing 50% of the
job, which is action.
This is the example I want.
And this is the example to now
what do I want to get with this?
Well, if you just upload videos to YouTube
and you solve problems and you put a
normal title and a normal thumbnail,
you are most likely going to get views.
You don't have to be a
genius to the YouTube.
The main problem with YouTube
is it is a slower platform.
And how does that work?
Well, basically you will have to upload
videos for a longer period of time until you
actually see success.
Now, if at working at YouTube what you do
is you upload the four videos a week, you
have to upload, you eat well,
but also when you eat,
will you count your carbs?
And then you also edit your videos
and make them more appealing?
What you going to do is achieve that 80%
that no one is achieving, even 90, or in
sometimes a 100.
I don't believe in perfection,
but sometimes happens with this.
What I want to tell you is that YouTube is
half the job consistency and half the job
quality. I already gave you the quality.
All you gotta do now is put
the action in with consistency.
I hope that this video helped you a
lot and you learned how to use YouTube.
I'll see you in the next class
on the Adam Swift course.
Bye bye.